mobidoom.com 2015-05-10

# Privacy Policy - Mobi Doom

At Mobidoom.com, we realize that privacy of your personal information is important. Is an info on what types of personal information we get and collect when you use and check out Mobidoom.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never offer your individual information to third parties.

**Log Files**

We gather and use the data contained in log data files, just like most other websites. The information within the log documents include your IP address (Internet process) street address, your Internet service provider (world wide web company, like Shaw or AOL Cable tv), the internet browser you used to visit our site (including World wide web Explorer or Firefox), enough time you frequented our website and which pages you frequented all through our website.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Mobidoom.com does not use any cookies to store information for now

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

**Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site.**

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on Mobidoom.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Mobidoom.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. Mobidoom.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
